The important thing is there?.
The reason why it's there is?.
I will protect you!.
Okay, let's go ahead and go ahead!.
The moon will always come to the moon!.
The moon will come to the moon!.
Let's look at the moon?.
Ha-ha-ha!
We're almost to the exit now!
Full speed ahead until we fly out of here!
What?
No way!
You're getting right!
All right, there it is!
Time to move out, men!
Let's charge ahead, join them,
and get Franky back! Yeah!
City! Gomorrah! Jump!
Straw Hat!
The entire Franky family
thanks you for helping us!
We'll never forget it!
Fire the connection cannon!
Cool!
Hey, nice job!
Pretty high-class bullets you got there!
Awesome!
Damn it!
You stupid bastards!
You idiot, you gotta be more careful!
Ah, looks like it drifted a bit, huh?
Listen, I know these sea trains
like the back of my hand.
I'll find that railway.
Found ya! Let's go!
Attention!
This train will soon be on the railway!
Once we are our acceleration
will increase exponentially.
Find something to hold on to so we
can keep the injuries to a minimum.
A minimum will be injured regardless?
Listen, you!
Behave yourself! Whoa!
That was close, Granny!
A little to the right!
Yeah!
Don't you worry.
I'll get it right next time.
You'll see. Huh?
Chisney! Candy!
No!
I left you with iceberg!
How could this have happened?
Get out from there and come inside!
You'll be blown away out there!
We're fine! We're fine!
Candy!
Ha-ha-ha!
I'm gonna fall!
Whatever you do, don't let go! I'm flying!
Wait!
Hold on a second, okay?
Let me slow down!
Huh?
Oh, no! I forgot!
No brakes!
We can't stop!
Whoa, what the heck?
Hey, that kind of looks like fun!
Ha!
Look, it's the Straw Hat guy! Hey!
Hurry!
Grab those two and bring them inside!
Once this train hits the
railway, they'll be blown away!
Right!
No! No!
I thought I was a goner!
You almost were!
I said, if you don't come inside,
you're gonna get blown away!
Oh, that speed was crazy. Told ya.
He's right, that was rough.
Oh, hurt my back.
Hold on a second.
There are a few more people
in here than there should be.
Yeah?
Who do you mean?
He means you!
I mean you, too!
I tried, but no matter what I
said or did, I couldn't stop you.
And the enemy that you'd go
through all of this to rescue your
friend from is the exact same
one that tried to kill Iceberg.
I've got a word or two of my own I want
to say to those bastards. Ha ha ha! Yeah!
You're not the only one!
We figured that if we snuck
onto the train and followed you,
we'd be right behind you when things
went down with those Newgate assassins!
So here we are.
Seems our hunch was right.
Let us join you.
We want to avenge Iceberg.
Sounds like we all have a common enemy.
They're the same ones that
kidnapped our bro Franky!
Yeah, he's right.
No point in playing dumb.
We know exactly who they are.
Hey, Galley-La!
If anything happens to him,
it's gonna be on your shoulders.
Can it.
Iceberg's the one that's
endured the most here.
Hey!
What the heck are they talking about?
Come on!
There's something you're
not telling us, Paulie!
Yeah, it's time to come clean.
Tell us everything.
We need answers.
You know who the true culprit is.
We're not stupid, you know.
We got a pretty good idea who it is.
You're not gonna surprise us.
Well, I guess the story about them
disappearing was too convenient.
Fine, I'll tell you.
The true identities of those masked men
are Luchi, Kaku, Khalifa,
and Bluno from the bar.
It was them.
They're the ones who
tried to kill Iceberg.
Are you telling me you
never even thought of them?
You said they went back to their hometown.
Come on, you believe that?
We thought it was Michael and
Hoykel from the Backstreet District.
Roar!
Who the hell are they?
What?
You're kidding.
You've never heard of them?
They're pretty famous in the Backstreet.
Roar! Roar!
Why would half the foreman
leave in the middle of a crisis?
That really hit the spot.
Man, I was starving.
Right. So,
even though we got in a few
fights back in town with
both the Franky family and
with the Galley-La shipwrights,
the enemy we're all going
after here is one and the same.
Now, the strongest one, the
toughest out of all of them,
is definitely that pigeon guy.
He's mine.
I'm going to beat the crap out of him.
Luffy's right.
This is a battle to get
back what those four
goons from the world
government took from us.
So, we either reach them in time
or all of this will be for nothing.
Granny, look!
It's Akula Call!
It's here already?
Hey, let me take a look.
Oh no!
Hey, shouldn't you be in
the engine room right now?
You've got to find some way
to dodge that gigantic wave!
Uh-uh!
Rocket Man can't be controlled, remember?
We can't adjust the speed, use
the brakes, or change our course.
My job ended as soon as I
got us up on the railway.
Trains lined up on the
tracks, running at full speed,
and there's nothing
anybody can do to stop it!
No.
Hey, if we don't do something
and fast, this train's gonna...
Everybody on this train
has the exact same goal.
There's no point in fighting separately.
Yeah, he's right.
From this point forward, we fight as one.
There are two more of my
crew on that other train.
Once we've caught up to them, our
fighting force will be even stronger.
Listen up!
We're not going to let
that big wave beat us!
We will achieve our goal!
Let's go!
All right, boys, why don't you show me what
you can do about that wave? You got it!
Fire all cannons!
Blow it to man! Rawr!
Turn it to my special tank!
It's just water!
Don't be afraid, bros!
Prepare the cannon! Roger!
Get a move on!
Oh, the transponder snail's ringing.
Hey, you there?
Yes, Captain T-Bone.
How did you get that
injury on your arm? Huh?
Oh. This?
I got bitten by a bug earlier,
and it bled when I scratched it.
How awful!
We must staunch the bleeding.
We'll have to make do with this.
Sir, you don't have to
tear your cape just for me.
It may be your arm that's bleeding.
But when one of my men is injured,
It's my heart that hurts the most.
Captain, thank you!
Let us fill today and every
day forth With good deeds!
So that peace and kindness shall reign.
This race is still really scary?
Captain!
I'll help.
Oh, good.
But let me explain the problem.
first.
If there's anything I can do, even
if it kills me, I will protect you.
Aw, thanks.
But the problem is with the
officials at Car 6 and 7.
They were completely wiped out.
Not only that, the two criminals
detained in Car 6 are missing.
That's awful!
We can't tell if the
prisoners escaped on their
own or if they were helped
by an unknown intruder.
For heaven's sake, man,
start a rescue operation.
Help the injured and spread
the word to the other cause.
Yes, sir.
Nami.
Nami, can you hear me? Yeah.
What's going on, Sanji?
I've got some bad news.
Things have gotten complicated.
What do you mean?
Hey, wait a sec.
What was that noise?
Is someone there with you or something?
It's nothing.
Just some dumbass. Huh? Say what?
Sanji, what's that noise?
Sounds like a bunch of screaming.
Are you OK over there?
What do you mean by dumbass?
Sorry, dumbass is actually.
Roar!
Jimmy Turner!
Leave it to us!
Not even making a dent.
I should've figured.
You think those puny
things are gonna work?
Everybody step back!
Let the Franky family's
special cannon do its stuff!
Target!
Aqua Laguna!
Go!
Super Scrap Cannon fire!
Fire again! Don't let him!
Bring more cannonballs!
Got it! Aim at the center!
Focus on one spot! Focus, focus!
Give it all you got!
Yeah, good luck with that.
By the way, the tracks do rise up a bit,
but not enough to get us over that wave.
Rocket Man has done pretty well out here
so far, but if we get hit, we're finished.
Does that mean we're all gonna die?
No guarantees.
I warned you now, didn't I?
What?
I don't want to die!
I see.
They still have Robin.
Sounds like things are pretty
lively on your end, too.
Hey, listen, Sanji.
I need to tell you why
Robin's doing all this.
And also why everyone's
screaming for that matter.
Shut up!
So, like I was just saying, we
found out why Robin's with CP9.
We're out here trying to follow her,
but things are kind of crazy right now.
It's a long story.
We're all gonna die!
But I don't wanna die!
Me either!
If you have time to cry, keep firing!
We'll find a way out!
Hey, Muffy.
Yeah, I know what you're thinking.
That wave's asking for it, huh?
Come on!
Keep those cannons firing!
What are you guys planning on doing?
Same thing as you.
What?
Hey, how much is 108 times 2?
216.
216, huh?
That's too long.
Can't we round up or something?
Fine.
Make it 300, then.
I don't get it.
What do they think they're doing?
If cannons don't work, what
could our swords gonna do?
Well, they did say we should
keep fighting, though.
Stop yapping and back them up! Roger!
Okay! Ready?
Uh-huh.
Go, go, go!
Three hundred caliber!
We're going to crash!
Turn it out!
Let's go.
We made it!
Take them, Aqualaguna!
No!
I thought we were going to die!
Hey, hey, Nami, are you okay?
Yeah, I think so.
We survived after all, huh?
You pirates know how to party.
Keep up the good work.
They're even stronger than Aqua Laguna.
If we were enemies, I'd be scared right
now, but since we're friends, I'm happy!
Those will have!
We'd all be dead right
now if not for them.
Lucky that little trick worked.
Let's not get ahead of
ourselves, everybody!
We're not through the
storm yet! Yes, ma 'am!
I'm not afraid of anything anymore!
Wow, that was really fun!
I knew you were strong, but
that was something else!
Are you an alien or something?
Because that was totally
out of this world!
Oops, sorry about that.
Luffy, come here a sec! Huh? Huh?
Sanji wants to talk.
That you, Luffy?
Yep, it's me!
What's up?
You saved Robin?
No, sorry.
Afraid I'm still working on that one.
Nami just told me why Robin
surrendered and all that stuff.
So yeah I know I see that's good well
anyway you know what's next go ahead!
Give him hell son he'll die if he
fights them now if he wants to stand a
chance he's gotta wait for us some of
the guys on that train are really tough
It's fine if it was you
you wait if you were
on that train right now instead of him and
I told you that robin
sacrificed herself to
protect us would you sit
there and do nothing?
No use trying to stop it!
Read me like a book but thanks moss head I
never knew that you cared
about me so much I hope
I kill you anyway that
settles it I was willing
to fight for robin even before I knew the?
truth.
But now that you told me how she really
feels, I wouldn't stop even if you begged
me.
Why'd you break it, you bastard?
I wanted to talk to
Straw Hat too, damn it!
Huh?
Deal with it.
No point in griping at me now.
What, was I supposed to
interrupt while you were
talking?
That's just rude!
You're rude anyway.
I hope he's okay on his own.
Granny, hurry!
Make the train go faster!
Faster?
Yeah!
More like...
You know?
Oh, don't you worry.
This baby is already going way
faster than it was ever supposed to.
In fact, we're going so fast
we can't even stop anymore.
so much stuff has happened since i left it
almost doesn't seem real
in a way robin's in the
same boat you are never
found out about what
happened with the mary
or your fight with luffy
it makes me ashamed to think it but while
we were busy fighting amongst ourselves
Robin surrendered to the government
so the six of us can be safe.
That includes you
Why are you crying?
I'm not crying, you are!
Damn it!
Now I'm all torn up!
I always thought Robin
was some evil monster,
but it turns out she's got a soft side!
What if I'm confused
about other stuff, too?
How am I supposed to go on?
I'm not gonna stand here in
the rain when Robin's so close.
I've gotta save her before
it's too late. Sweet!
Once again, I'm Franky,
leader of the Franky family.
You and me will make a
good team, I promise, bro.
Well,
I won't go into the details,
but I got a pretty good reason to keep
robbing away from those government chumps,
too.
Besides, you really touched my
heart with that story of yours.
Hey, Long Nose, let's do this thing!
No.
I'm not coming.
This doesn't have anything
to do with me anymore.
You're about to make yourselves personal
enemies of the world government.
I don't want to be any part of that.
Besides, Luffy and the rest
of the crew are coming.
After I humiliated
myself in front of them,
I just can't pretend like nothing
ever happened and laugh it off.
I still feel bad for Robin, but I'm sorry.
It's not my job to save her anymore.
I am not a part of Loopy's crew!
See ya.
See ya?
There's no place to go!
Come on!
You guys can talk this over, bro!
Forget it.
Just leave him.
You are both stubborn as hell.
Check every corner!
They gotta be here somewhere!
What?
This is just terrible!
We'll have to make do with this!
The train's in a lot of trouble right now.
Wanzek, we need your help.
Shut up, stupid!
Your face is in trouble!
Nero!
The criminal's made an escape!
They're right here!
Damn it, they found us!
Metallic Star!
Who the hell are you?
Your friend told me everything.
I understand that you're here to
rescue a certain mademoiselle.
That alone is reason enough
for me to join your cause.
My weapons are at your disposal.
My name is Sniper King!